nnu.com 2015-04-09

# Privacy Policy | NetNearU

## WiFi Network Privacy Policy

NetNearU (“NNU,” “we” or “us”) knows that users of its WiFi network communications services and related services and features (the “Service”) care about the personal information they provide to us. This privacy policy, which is part of our WiFi Network Terms and Conditions of Use (“T&C’s”), is designed to provide you with information about how we collect, store and use personally identifiable information obtained through our web site. We refer to this information as “personal information.” NNU reserves the right to revise this privacy policy from time to time, and by using the Service, you are agreeing to the terms of the then-current privacy policy.

## How Information Is Collected

When you log on or register to use the Service, we may ask you for information such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, or other login information as required by a carrier or venue partner and certain demographic information. 

NNU uses “cookies.” A “cookie” is a text file, invoked by standard browser software, that we place on your hard drive to enable our systems to, among other things, recognize your browser, track transactions, and allow you to navigate our web site or the Internet through a WiFi network that we manage without your having to re-enter information. The information gathered by cookies is not made available to organizations. We may also automatically receive and store certain other types of information, such as the type of web browser you use or the pages you browse to.

## Use Of Information We Collect

Personal information collected by NNU may be used by NNU to communicate with you, register you as a user and to use the Service without having to re-enter information, administer the Service, comply with applicable law, and as otherwise provided in this privacy policy. We may occasionally make personal information available to select other organizations, including but not limited to, affiliated organizations, agents working on our behalf, companies or organizations with whom we have a contractual or sponsor relationship, or in connection with an asset transfer. We may also provide aggregated data to these and other organizations. Although we may make reasonable inquiries to determine that such other organizations maintain privacy policies comparable to ours, we are not responsible for the enforcement of such policies.

## Third-Party Service Providers

NNU may engage reputable third-party vendors in order to help us manage the Service and allow us to better assist our users. These may include third-party vendors engaged to analyze, for marketing purposes, the information collected by NNU.

## Administration Of Our Service/Compliance With Law

We may disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our T&C’s or to protect the safety, property or other rights of our users or the public. In addition, we may disclose or access account information for administrative and other purposes that we believe are necessary to develop, maintain, and improve our products and services. We also may disclose your personal information if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, a subpoena, or other legal process.

## Security Used To Protect Your Information

We take commercially reasonable steps to maintain the security of customer information via a variety of access controls, including password protection, electronic firewalls, and data encryption. However, NNU does not guarantee the security of such information.

## Third-Party Web Sites

You may access other web sites through the Service, but NNU is not responsible for the privacy policies, terms and conditions of use, or content of any such web sites. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy policies and terms and conditions of use of such web sites.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

NNU may revise this privacy policy from time to time. We encourage you to visit this page periodically to review our current policy so that you will always know what information we gather and how we may use that information.
